I am Haruna Sakamoto, the team president.
And,
I am Shinji Yoshida, Mrs. Generata.
Pleased to meet you.
This is a continuation from yesterday.
This is the third time,
This time, we have a project that has become a regular feature in the nighttime conversation series between idols and idols,
This is a question from an idol to an idol.
We've seen a lot of different ones from everyone so far, but now it's our turn,
We asked them to prepare questions they would like to ask each other,
I've prepared them.
Oh, wow.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, I would like to ask Shinjuku-chan a question first,
She's so cute, isn't she? Well, I'd like to ask Pearl a question first.
She's so cute, isn't she?
It's the same when I talked to her both times,
We've been talking about it at our live performances and on our social networking sites. It's all cute videos.
Was it her birthday?
Recently.
When we had the birthday service, it was also a lot.
Well, thank you very much.
It's so cute.
I wondered what you keep in mind most when you are on stage.
When I'm on stage,
I wonder.
I would like to ask her what she does when she is on stage.
I am the one who wants to know,
No, no, no, there are many idols,
I think that even if you really throw out idols, they all have their own individuality. They all have their own individuality,
And of course, the way they present themselves is the same,
I think they are all cute and amazing,
From your point of view, Pearl.
Yes, I agree. I think that Tohoku-san's songs are rather cool,
I have an image that Touhoku has many cool songs and cool dances,I think there is an image that there are a lot of cool dances,
I thought it would be nice if I could show femininity in a cool song,
I'm always a bit conscious of saying the opposite.
That's interesting. Yes, that's true.
I'm always conscious of the fact that I have to decide what to do in a cool way. Wow, that's interesting. Indeed.
There are 9 of us, so we all have to look good,
There are nine of us, so we all have to look good, right?
Yes, yes.
As a color.
That's true.
But I have an image of Pearl's lines being very beautiful,
Well, thank you very much.
I wonder if it's because I'm conscious of it.
Yes, that's right. I am conscious of it. I'm relatively conscious of it.
During lessons or while looking in the mirror?
I am conscious of it while looking in the mirror,
Also, I think I can make my hair look like that when I let it flutter,
So I am conscious of little things like that.
That's amazing.
You look really cool.
The way you make your hair flutter.
I'm curious about that.
The other way around? Did you hear it yourself?
I am curious.
But I think it's a good idea to make eye contact with everyone who is there,
You have a great sense of live performance,
You usually feel a great sense of togetherness,
I think that no matter where you are, the feeling of oneness is always there,
I think a sense of togetherness can be created anywhere at a live concert,
I don't want people to feel that they are not united because their tickets were purchased at the back of the venue, so I always make sure not to let down my guard from corner to corner,
So I always make it a point to watch the audience from corner to corner,
I'm aware that I have to watch every corner.
I can feel it.
I always see the mark of the great sense of unity,
That's what I'm doing.
But then again, there is also the regional group,But, you know, there are regional groups,
I'm going to do it from the local area,
I can feel the enthusiasm of the local people,
I see Mr. Totoku always doing what he says he is doing.
I think he's good at what he does,
You have that kind of thing, don't you?
Yes, there is. Yes, I think so.
Lately, I've been coming to Tokyo more and more often,
We've been talking about what we should do in order not to lose to Tokyo.
We all play those games together, don't we?
Yes, we do.
You don't talk about it much?
I'd like to hear about it.
What do you mean?
Among the members.
Well, we've been meeting a lot.
Since we became acquainted with the company...
We have always wanted to be a group that leads the way because orcas are the top marine life form,
We often have discussions with all the managers in the team.
We often discuss what we are going to do and what the members think about it.
I think it is difficult. It is difficult, isn't it?
There are many different opinions, and of course, even among the four of us, there are times when they differ,
It is more difficult when there are many people,
I agree. There are many opinions,
But, strangely enough, when they come together as one, they come together as one,
I could hear deep conversations about how they want to make it better and what they want to do in the end. 、、、、、、 I would like to ask a question from Kitchenstay Sindhu.
I have an image of rap music and dance as well,
Indeed. In the songs, you know.
Yes, that's right. Because recently, TOKU-san has been doing more and more rap songs,
So I wondered how I should rap.
I was like, "Wow, how do you say that? I love it,
I'm glad.
Recently, I went to Yuzuki's hair booth a while ago,
I was asked the same question by Amemura-chan,
I think everyone is cool,
Rap music is difficult, isn't it? It's difficult to rap so fast.Rap is difficult, isn't it? You have to say it fast.
Yes, it is. But I'm going to jump out and interrupt you,
I'm glad. If you say so.
But it wasn't until after I opened up that it became easier to understand and strengthened, like being in charge of rapping,
Even before that, there were times when I would meet him in a song,
But, if you are a dancer or have this sense of rhythm,
You know what they say about groove.
I think that was often chosen by the group as well, because that kind of thing is engraved in the music,
I had a lot of people tell me that,
It's okay.
It's the groove, isn't it?
A sense of groove.
Yes, from various people,
You don't listen to hip-hop much, do you?
Or music?
I do listen to it.
Listen?
I listen to really good-looking people, women and men,
Rap music is really free, isn't it?
There are people who are really cool online, and there are people who are really cool off the Internet,
There are people who are really cool, and there are people who go "Taka Taka Taka Taka Taka",
So, I don't think there is any set rule,
I don't think there are any rules, so I think it's up to you to be yourself, and your voice is no different,
Ah~
If you could rap in your own way, that would be your strength.
I think so.
I'm learning a lot.
It's the same with the dancing you mentioned earlier,
Of course the nine of you can sing, but there's also the way you showcase your rapping,
The lines!
The lines part. The song.
The lines in the cute songs that make people melt,
Basically, do you select the recording after everyone else has done it?
Or are the parts divided up in advance?
Are the parts divided in advance?
Most of the time, the parts are divided in advance,I often have them partitioned in advance,
I deliberately and intentionally took all of them, just the echires part.
After that, we decided who would go and what would happen,
It's like that.
The chosen one.
That's not true.
It was just luck.
But the feeling of being grabbed in an instant..,
I'm still thinking.
Because it's amazing,
I'm glad.
It gradually evolved from a line to a lapper,
And it's getting longer.
It's new.
I think that when you think you've got the right line, you can go from there to a cool rap.
There might be.
I'd like to see it.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I heard your precious story. Thank you. I'm glad. I'd like to see it. I'll do my best.
I heard your precious story.
Thank you. I'm glad.
Let's talk again slowly.
Thank you.
And now that we've heard each other's questions,
There will be an event in Osaka on September 30 featuring three groups that we are a part of, we are Team Saiji, and Ikinari Tohoku-san, and x Shoujo-tai.
Yay!
The title,
Sapura Localism Vol. 3
Let's make it a sister city!
Osaka Takoyaki City
Yay!
I wonder which one is it?
3 or 3? - Ah, volume!
Volume, because it's in English.
It looks like a 3, doesn't it?
Volume 3.
That's how everyone looks at 3.And that's how you all started looking at 3.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's been a little while since I've seen a Roncalism.
It's been a while.
I've been thinking about what kind of event I want to do.
I'd like to do it next time.
But, Maso-san, you want to do a shuffle unit, don't you?
I want to!
All the groups would be shuffled,
That's for sure.
We had separate groups when we were in the "Anti-magic ninja" group,
But we didn't do anything with them, did we?
That's right.
I would certainly like to do it this time,
I would like to do it this time.
I would like to do it this time. By all means. Please do.
By all means.
That's something you don't see very often.
Yes, it is. It's very necessary.
It might be rare.
When we do a medley or something like that with all the staff,
We do it sometimes,
But we do a whole song from each of the three groups,
Do you want to do it?
Yes. It would be nice if we could do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
We are looking forward to seeing you all in Osaka on September 30.
I look forward to seeing you all in Osaka on September 30.
So, we have had three conversations,
Is today the last one?
I am sad to say.
We didn't have much to talk about so far,
But we did have a lot of fun together at the end of the year, like when we were working together on the Peach Color Candy,
We were close to each other a lot.
That's for sure. Yes, we did. Like while we were waiting.Indeed. There was, wasn't there? Like while I was waiting.
I felt safe when I was close to them.
It's easier to talk to him when you talk to him,
Really?
I'm glad.
I was nervous at first, too,
I was nervous at first, but now that we've had a chance to talk, I feel like we've opened up.
I feel like we're getting to know each other.
You are so cute. You really are.
I look forward to working with you again.
So, thank you all for watching.
Thank you very much.
My partners so far are Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shachi and,
Ms. Shinju Yoshida from Lifetime Talk.
Bye bye!